Guide to the F. C. C. Boyd Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
F. C. C. Boyd autograph collection
1635-1934
MS 942
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
Chiefly an autograph collection of approximately three hundred letters, two United States Navy Department letterbooks (1873-1876), photographs, drawings, and a small amount of F. C. C. Boyd's financial papers. Most of the items are American, although several are European, including one signed by Pope Urban VIII. Major topics covered by the colletion include numismatics, the theater, and the United States Navy.
Boyd, F. C. C.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of F. C. C. Boyd, 1941.
Scope and Contents
The F.C.C. Boyd Autograph Collection contains approximately three hundred letters and other documents ranging in date from 1635 to 1934, arranged in alphabetical order. Although most of the papers are American in origin, several are signed by Europeans, including one document issued by Pope Urban VIII. Major topics covered by the collection include numismatics, the theater, and the United States Navy. Two Navy Department letterbooks (1873-1876) are included with the autograph letters.
Aside from autograph letters, the collection offers a miscellany of autographs cut from various documents, printed matter, photographs and drawings, and a visitors' book from the National Hobby Collectors Show Numismatic Exhibit of 1934-1935. There is, in addition, a small amount of financial papers pertaining to F.C.C. Boyd.
This autograph collection was donated to Yale University by F.C.C. Boyd in 1941.
Numismatics; Theater; Autographs; United States. Navy
- Inventory, 1635-1938, undated; 1.5 linear feet (4 boxes, 1 folio)
  - Autograph Letters
    - Abbot, Gorham Dummer (1807-1874), 1856 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Eli, 1817 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Aldrich, Nelson Wilmarth (1841-1915), 1883 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alexander, George, 1874 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, Samuel Davis (1819-1894), 1875 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Allen, William (1784-1868), 1805 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - American Numismatic Association (printed matter), 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1827 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ammen, Daniel (1819-1898), 1874-1876 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Anderson, Mabel, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Anderson, Martin Brewer (1815-1890), 1858 August 28 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Anthon, Philip H. (1825-1861), undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Armsby, James H. (1809-1875), 1858 Sep, December (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Auldjo, Thomas, 1807 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Averett, Thomas H., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bailey, William, 1868 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Baldwin, Briscoe Gerald (1789-1862), 1842 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ball, William L., 1822 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Barbour, John Strode (1790-1855), 1831, 1846 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Barkhorn, Henry C., Jr., 1934 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Barnard, Charles (1838-1920), 1895 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Barnes, Albert (1798-1870), 1866 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Barton, Richard W. (1800-1860), 1841 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bassett, Burnell (1764-1841), 1822 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bayly, Thomas Henry (1810-1856), 1848 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Beale, James Madison Hite (1786-1866), 1850 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Bigelow, Jacob (1786-1879), undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Billings, Silas (1804-1881), 1842 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Binney, Amos (1803-1847), 1846 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Black, C. F., 1880 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Blake, William Phipps (1825-1910), 1869 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Boggs, T., 1845 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Borden, R. N., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bosworth, Francke Huntington (1843-1925), undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Bradbury, James Ware (1802-1901), 1884 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Bradford, John M., 1811 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Bradstreet, Mrs. Martha, 1836 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Bratton, James H., 1832 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Brett, John, 1863 January 20 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Brewer, William Henry (1828-1910), 1874 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Brough and Boncicault, 1890, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Buell, Don Carlos (1818-1898), 1854 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Burden, James A., 1860 December 24 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Burroughs, Marie, 1895-1896, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Bushnell, A., 1876 Mar, April (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Butler, Jonas, and Lucy Ann, 1836 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      General
      See also: Folio, box 5
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1901-1902 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Cadwalader, John L. (1805-1879), 1875 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Calhoun, J. H., and W. B., 1833 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Cameron, Edgar Spier (1862-1944), [1893] (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Campbell, Archibald, 1874 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Cargill, Henry A., 1847 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Carlisle, John Griffin (1835-1910), 1888 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Cecil, Sackville A., undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Chadwick, French Ensor (1844-1919), 1899 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Chapman, Lucian Thorp, 1895 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Chapman, M. P., undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
      - Chace, Jonathan (1829-1917), 1885 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Chester, Peter (1717-1799), 1777 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Clark, J., 1851 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Clarke, D. [K.?], 1857 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Cole, Cornelius (1822-1924), 1864 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Colton, Simeon, 1824 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Columbia University: Trustees, 1870 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Comegys, William, 1827 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Comstock, George Z., 1865 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Cook, Henry C. M., 1891 March 24 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Cotton, Charles S., 1890 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Cowdin, Elliot C., 1876 January 7 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Cox, Edward Travers (1821-1907), 1871 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Creighton, W. E., undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Cullen, Henry J., Jr., 1881 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Dacre, Arthur C[ulver] J[ames], undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Dana, Samuel W. (1760-1830), 1818 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Darling, C. W., 1864 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Darling, William, 1853 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Davis, Matthew L. (1773-1850), 1818 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Davison, L. A., 1861 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Deblois, ____, 1793 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - DeWolfe, Elsie Anderson, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch, 1885 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Dietz, Linda, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Dougherty, Daniel, 1881 January - May (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Drury, Eunice, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Duane, Abraham, James, and Cornelius, 1759 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Duffield, F. G., 1909 August 22 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Dutcher, S. B., 1861 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Farley, John, 1864 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Fay, Samuel A., 1842 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Fellows, John R., 1889 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Finch-Kelly, Florence, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Forbes, Charles E., 1862 July 4 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Foulke, William Dudley, 1890 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Frelinghuysen, Frederick J., 1876 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Friars Club, [New York?] (printed matter), 1908 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Gaspari, Gaetano (1807-1881), 1854 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Getz, James Lawrence, 1821-1891, 1867 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Gilder, Jeanette Leonard (1849-1916), 1896 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Goto, Shimpei, 1902 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Gray, Jeannet, with Agnes Raine and William Scott, 1844 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Greenough, Richard Saltonstall (1819-1904), 1848 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Grolier Club, New York, 1893 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Gross, Emily B., undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Hall, Joshua, 1875 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Hamburg, Germany: St. Nicholas Church, 1877 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Harlan, James (1820-1899), 1864 July 23 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Harman, A. W., Jr., 1887 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - [Harkness?], John, 1858 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Harvey, James E., 1875 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Havilland, E., 1849 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Hay, Henry H., 1887 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Hewitt, Hiram S., 1884 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Higgins, Frank C., 1909 February 4, undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Hovenden, Helen Carson, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Howell, James Bruen (1816-1880), 1870 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1909 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Hunt, Freeman (1804-1858), 1854 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Huntt, H., 1831, 1833 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Irwin, John H., 1819 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Jones, H. Madison, 1884 August 17, undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Julian, George Washington, 1817-1899, 1862 January 2 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Keith, Isaac Stockton, 1809 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - King, Rufus (1755-1827), 1821 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Knox, J. Rice, undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - LaBau, N. B., 1852 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Lancaster, Pennsylvania: Mayor, Nathaniel Lightner, 1827 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Latham, Edwin, 1858 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Lathrop, T. K., undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Lawrence, Amos Adams (1814-1886), 1849 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Lawrence, Nicholas, 1802 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Lawrence, William (1819-1899), 1875 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Lawson, Oscar Alexander (1818-1854), 1850, undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Lawton, Sanford, 1832 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Lee, Kenneth, 1894 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Lee, Thomas J., 1850 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Lee, W. Raymond, 1853 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Leslie, C. M. S., 1873 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Lester, Charles Edwards (1815-1890), 1886 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Levering, Joseph, 1871 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Lewis, William Berkeley (1784-1866), 1838 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Lightner, Nathaniel
      See: box 2, folder 125
    - Lloyd, Demarest, 1871 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Loring, F. W., 1873 January 3 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Loring, George Bailey (1817-1891), 1882 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Lowrey, Sarrah, 1806 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Lunt, Micajah, Jr., 1826 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Mabie, Hamilton W., 1898 January 11 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - McClelland, Martha, 1793 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - McDonald, J. N., 1894 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Macomb, J. N., 1855 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Maryland: Governor, Philip F. Thomas, 1848 August 11 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Maryland: Governor, Robert Wright, 1808 Apr, September (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Mason, Charles (1804-1882), 1853 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Merrill, H. W., 1836-1837, 1862 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Miles, Pliny, 1859 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Miller, Jacob Welsh (1800-1862), 1845 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Mitchell, T. V., 1879 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Moses, James C., 1858, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Moses, James C., and P. H., 1891 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Moses family, undated (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Mysenburg, Josephine, undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - National Arts Club, 1905 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Nelson, Jonathan, 1857 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Neumann, Katherine L., undated (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Neville, E., 1854, 1856 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Newman, Mary O., 1852 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - New York (City): Department of Public Works, Bureau of Water Register, 1881 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - New York (State): Adjutant general, Franklin Townsend, 1878 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - New York Numismatics Club (printed matter), 1915 March 4 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Oberholtzer, Ellis Paxton (1868-1936), 1907 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - O'Neill, John Joseph (1846-1898), 1884 August 1 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Ord, George
      See: box 1, folder 8
    - Owen, David Dole (1807-1860), 1852 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Owen, William Florence (1844-1906), 1893 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Packard, Alpheus Spring (1798-1884), 1875 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Page, Thomas Jefferson (1808-1899), 1845 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Paget, Walpurga Ehrengarde Helena, Countess de Hohenthal, [1883 Feb] (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Payne, James S., 1876 February 21, 22 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Peabody, Andrew Preston (1811-1893), 1859, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Pearce, James Alfred (1805-1862), 1861 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Pearson, Jonathan (1813-1887), 1885 September 15 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Pendleton, George Hunt (1825-1889), 1859 March 21 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Pennington, Alexander Cumming McWhorter (1810-1867), 1856 April 20 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, Philadelphia, 1889 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Perkins, Thomas H. (1810-1849), 1833 February 16 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Perry, Amos, 1881 December 3 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Phoenix, Stephen Whitney (1839-1881), undated (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Pinkney, Jonathan, 1795 August 14 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Platt, Jonas, 1820 April 18 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Pleasonton, S., 1822 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Poland, Luke Potter (1815-1887), 1875 February 4 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Pomeroy Theodore Medad (1824-1905), 1860 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Porter, John Addison (1866-1900), 1897 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - Porter, John K., 1883 November 29 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - Portugal: Vice-Consulate, New York, Joaquim José Vasques, Jr., 1814 October 14 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - Pratt, Thomas George (1804-1869), 1842 September 2 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - Preston, William Ballard (1805-1862), 1849 July 23 (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Pryor, John, 1781 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Purnell, William Henry (1826-1902), 1859 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Putnam, Jonathan Pickering, 1876 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - Raine, Agnes
      See: box 1, folder 99
    - Randall, A., 1843 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Randall, Samuel Jackson (1828-1890), 1875-1888 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Redwood, William, 1766 June 5 (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Reeves, J. S. K.
      See: box 2, folder 242
    - Richardson, William, 1859 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Riddle, George Read (1817-1867), 1853 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - Ridgely, Charles Goodwin (1784-1848), 1844 June 27 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Robertson, Morgan Andrew (1861-1915), undated
      See: Folio, box 5
    - Robeson, George Maxwell (1829-1897), 1874-1876 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Robinson, Lucius
    - Roche, James Jeffrey (1847-1908), 1895 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Romero, José, 1899 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - Royce, N., 1840 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Runnels, Hardin R.
    - Russell, John L., 1840 September (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Russell, William Hamilton (1856-1907), [ca. 1893 May 17] (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Salisbury, Stephen, 1863 January 9 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Savage Club, London (printed matter), 1880 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Schmucker, Samuel Simon (1799-1873), 1869 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Schuyler, Eugene
    - Scott, John (1782-1861), 1825 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Scott, William
    - Searle, Arthur (1837-1920), 1870 February 7 (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - Seillière, Emma Riley Livermore, Baroness, undated (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - Semple, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 216)
    - Sergeant, John, 1806 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 217)
    - Sewell, J. C., 1879 September 11-29 (Box 2, Folder 218)
    - Short, Charles, 1885 November 20 (Box 2, Folder 219)
    - Sibley, John, 1812 March 8 (Box 2, Folder 220)
    - Sickels, David B., 1896-1897 (Box 2, Folder 221)
    - Simpson, John Palgrave (1807-1887), 1881 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 222)
    - Skinner, Mary, undated (Box 2, Folder 222)
    - Slingerland, John I., (1804-1861), 1856 August 18 (Box 2, Folder 223)
    - Smith, Albert, 1844 August 5 (Box 2, Folder 224)
    - Smith, Henry Boynton (1815-1877), 1853 January (Box 2, Folder 225)
    - Snyder, John (1793-1850), 1840 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 226)
    - Spofford, Ainsworth Rand (1825-1908), 1878 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 227)
    - Stephenson, Robert, 1854 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 228)
    - [Stone, John P.?], 1886 January 22 (Box 2, Folder 229)
    - Stone, Rev. John Seely (1795-1882), 1859 April 20 (Box 2, Folder 230)
    - Stoughton, Edwin Wallace (1818-1882), 1845 July 25 (Box 2, Folder 231)
    - Swackhamer, C., 1864 September 5 (Box 2, Folder 232)
    - Swann, Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 233)
    - Thomas, Francis (1799-1876), 1840, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 234)
    - Thomas, Philip F.
      See: box 2, folder 149
    - Thompson, Richard Wigginton (1809-1900), 1842 August 16 (Box 2, Folder 235)
    - Thulstrup, Thure de (1848-1930), 1893 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 236)
    - Townsend, Franklin
    - Towson, Nathan (1784-1854), 1830 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 237)
    - Tuck, Amos (1810-1879), 1871 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 238)
    - Tucker, M., 1850 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 239)
    - U.S. General Land Office: 7 bounty land patents, 1850-1860 (Box 2, Folder 240)
    - U.S. Legation, Greece: passport signed by Eugene Schuyler, 1883 February 21 (Box 2, Folder 241)
    - U.S. Military Academy, West Point, 1848 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 242)
    - Upshur, Abel Parker (1791-1844), 1842-1843 (Box 2, Folder 243)
    - Urban VIII, Pope (1568-1644), 1635 July [31] (Box 2, Folder 243)
    - Van Ness, John P., 1812 August 11 (Box 2, Folder 244)
    - Vansant, Joshua (1803-1884), 1854, 1858 (Box 2, Folder 245)
    - Vasques, Joaquin José
      See: box 2, folder 192
    - Vick, James, 1877 February 14 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Viguri, Luis de, 1803 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Wadsworth, Cornelia, undated (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Wakeman, Abram, 1864 October 19 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Wallace, Richard, 1853 April 7 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Wallis, Severn Teackle (1816-1891), 1878 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - Walter, Thomas Ustick (1804-1887), 1855 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Warner, Oliver, 1859 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Watson, Benjamin, 1869 November 24, undated (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Wedel, Karl, fürst von (1842-1919), undated
    - Weimar, John H., 1855 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    - Wendell, John L., 1820 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Wharton, Robert (1757-1834), 1817 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Wheatcroft, Nelson, undated (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Wheatley, W., 1865 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Wheeler, William Almon, 1819-1887, 1874 April 6 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Whyle, William Pinkney (1824-1908), 1872 August 9, undated (Box 3, Folder 261)
    - Wilkins, Charles, Jr., 1817 July 14 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    - Winans, Thomas DeKay (1820-1878), 1859 October 6 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - Winder, Levin (1757-1819), 1818 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Winner, William E., 1877 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Winthrop, Robert Charles (1809-1894), 1863 May 23 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Woodbridge, William (1780-1861), 1844, 1850 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Woodbury, Levi (1789-1851), 1841 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - Woodruff, J. C., 1868 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 269)
    - Woodward, W. Elliot, 1866 January 18 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - Worden, John Lorimer, 1818-1897, 1876 May 14, July 8 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    - Wright, Robert
      See: box 2, folder 150
    - Wright, Silas (1795-1847), 1845 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Young, Richard Montgomery (1798-1861), 1848 February 21 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    - Zerbe, Farran, 1909 August (Box 3, Folder 274)
    - Unidentified, 1860-1934, undated (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - U.S. Navy Department: letterbooks, 1873-1876 (Box 3, Folder 276-277)
  - Other Papers
    - Miscellaneous writings and notes by unidentified authors, 1902, undated (Box 3, Folder 278)
    - Miscellaneous autographs, 1853, 1892, undated (Box 3, Folder 279)
    - Calling cards, invitations, 1883-1907, undated (Box 3, Folder 280)
    - Receipts, 1830-1861, undated (Box 3, Folder 281)
    - Photographs and drawings, 1860, 1906, undated (Box 3, Folder 282)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1877-1878, 1914-1915, undated (Box 3, Folder 283)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1881-1885, 1910, undated (Box 3, Folder 284)
    - National Hobby Collectors Show: Numismatics Exhibit visitors' record, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Boyd, F.C.C.: Financial Papers
      - Checkbook, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 286)
      - Bills, receipts, checks, etc., 1934-1938 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Folio (Oversize Material) (Box 5)